Guide to the Robert Fridenberg Collection of Portrait and Topographical Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portraits, Series I
  - European Monarchs
    - France
      - Charles V, King of France, 1338-1380 (Box 230, Folder 3722)
      - Charles VI, King of France, 1368-1422 (Box 230, Folder 3723)
      - Charles VII, King of France, 1403-1461 (Box 230, Folder 3724)
      - Charles VIII, King of France, 1470-1498 (Box 230, Folder 3725)
      - Charles IX, King of France, 1550-1574 (Box 230, Folder 3726)
      - Charles X, King of France, 1757-1836 (Box 230, Folder 3727)
      - Childebert (all) (Box 230, Folder 3728)
      - Childeric (all) (Box 230, Folder 3729)
      - Chilpéric (all) (Box 230, Folder 3730)
      - Chlodio, ca. 392-448 (Box 230, Folder 3731)
      - Clotaire I, King of the Franks, ca. 497-561 (Box 230, Folder 3732)
      - Clotaire II, King of the Franks, 584-629 (Box 230, Folder 3733)
      - Clotaire III, King of the Franks, 652-673 (Box 230, Folder 3734)
      - Clovis, King of the Franks (Box 231, Folder 3735)
      - Dagobert I, King of the Franks, d. 639 (Box 231, Folder 3736)
      - Dagobert II, King of the Franks, ca. 650-679 (Box 231, Folder 3737)
      - Francis I, King of France, 1494-1547 (Box 231, Folder 3738)
      - Henry IV, King of France, 1553-1610, 3 (Box 231, Folder 3739-3741)
      - Marie de Médicis, Queen, consort of Henry IV, King of France, 1573-1642 (Box 231, Folder 3741a)
      - Hugh Capet, King of France, ca. 938-996 (Box 231, Folder 3742)
      - Jean II, King of France, 1319-1364 (Box 231, Folder 3743)
      - Lothair, King of France, 941-986 (Box 232, Folder 3744)
      - Louis I, Emperor, 778-840 (Box 232, Folder 3745)
      - Louis II, King of France, 846-879 (Box 232, Folder 3746)
      - Louis IV, King of France, 921-954 (Box 232, Folder 3747)
      - Louis V, King of France, 967?-987 (Box 232, Folder 3748)
      - Louis VI, King of France, 1078-1137 (Box 232, Folder 3749)
      - Louis X, King of France, 1289-1316 (Box 232, Folder 3750)
      - Louis XI, King of France, 1423-1483 (Box 232, Folder 3751)
      - Louis XIII, King of France, 1601-1643 (Box 232, Folder 3752)
      - Louis XIV, King of France, 1638-1715, 2 (Box 232, Folder 3753-3754)
      - Marie-Thérèse, Queen, consort of Louis XIV, King of France, 1638-1683 (Box 232, Folder 3754a)
      - Louis XV, King of France, 1710-1774, 3 (Box 233, Folder 3755-3757)
      - Louis XVI, King of France, 1754-1793, 4 (Box 233, Folder 3758-3761)
      - Marie Antoinette, Queen, consort of Louis XVI, King of France, 1755-1793, 3 (Box 234, Folder 3762-3764)
      - Louis XVII, of France, 1785-1795 (Box 234, Folder 3765)
      - Louis XVIII, King of France, 1755-1824, 2 (Box 234, Folder 3766-3767)
      - Louis XIX, King of France (Angoulême, Louis-Antoine d'Artois, duc d'), 1775-1844 (Box 234, Folder 3768)
      - Louis Philippe, King of the French, 1773-1850 (Box 235, Folder 3769)
      - Pepin, King of the Franks, d. 768 (Box 235, Folder 3770)
      - Pharamond, King of the Franks, ca. 370-427 (Box 235, Folder 3771)
      - Philippe I, King of France, 1052-1108 (Box 235, Folder 3772)
      - Philip II, King of France, 1165-1223 (Box 235, Folder 3773)
      - Philip III, King of France, 1245-1285 (Box 235, Folder 3774)
      - Philip IV, King of France, 1268-1314 (Box 235, Folder 3775)
      - Philip V, King of France, 1294-1322 (Box 235, Folder 3776)
      - Philip VI, King of France, 1293-1350 (Box 235, Folder 3777)
      - Thierry (all) (Box 235, Folder 3778)
      - Oversize
        - Caribert - Jean II, 20 (Box 236 (Oversize), Folder 3779-3798)
        - Louis IV - Thierry, 18 (Box 237 (Oversize), Folder 3799-3816)
    - Bonaparte family
      - Bonaparte family group (Box 238, Folder 3817)
      - Bonaparte, Carlo Maria, 1746-1785 (Box 238, Folder 3818)
      - Bonaparte, François-Charles-Joseph, Herzog von Reichstadt, 1811-1832 (Box 238, Folder 3819)
      - Bonaparte, Letizia, 1750?-1836 (Box 238, Folder 3820)
      - Bonaparte, Lucien, prince de Canino, 1775-1840 (Box 238, Folder 3821)
      - Bonaparte, Napoléon-Joseph-Charles-Paul, Prince, 1822-1891
      - Bonaparte, Paolina, 1780-1825 (Box 238, Folder 3822)
      - Caroline Bonaparte, consort of Joachim Murat, King of Naples, 1782-1839 (Box 238, Folder 3823)
      - Eugénie, Empress, consort of Napoleon III, Emperor of the French, 1826-1920 (Box 238, Folder 3824)
      - Hortense, Queen, consort of Louis Bonaparte, King of Holland, 1783-1837 (Box 238, Folder 3824a)
      - Jérôme Bonaparte, King of Westphalia, 1784-1860 (Box 238, Folder 3825)
      - Joachim Murat, King of Naples, 1767-1815 (Box 238, Folder 3826)
      - Joseph Bonaparte, King of Spain, 1768-1844 (Box 238, Folder 3827)
      - Josephine, Empress, consort of Napoleon I, Emperor of the French, 1763-1814, 2 (Box 238, Folder 3828-3829)
      - Louis Bonaparte, King of Holland, 1778-1846 (Box 238, Folder 3830)
      - María-Julia, Queen, consort of Joseph Bonaparte, King of Spain, 1771-1845
      - Marie Louise, Empress, consort of Napoleon I, Emperor of the French, 1791-1847, 2 (Box 239, Folder 3831-3832)
      - Napoleon I, Emperor of the French, 1769-1821
        - Allegorical portraits (Box 239, Folder 3833)
        - Astride a horse (Box 239, Folder 3834)
        - Bust portraits
          - After Francesco Cossia / Hilaire Le Dru (Box 239, Folder 3835)
          - After J. Guerin (Box 239, Folder 3836)
          - After Jean-Baptiste Isabey (Box 239, Folder 3837)
          - After Jacques-Louis David (Box 239, Folder 3838)
          - After François Gérard (Box 239, Folder 3839)
          - Profile, 2 (Box 239, Folder 3840-3841)
          - Three-quarter (Box 240, Folder 3842)
          - Frontal view (Box 240, Folder 3843)
        - Half-length portraits (Box 240, Folder 3844)
        - Full-length portraits
          - General (Box 240, Folder 3845)
          - In the field (Box 240, Folder 3846)
          - At the sea (Box 240, Folder 3847)
          - Seated (Box 240, Folder 3848)
        - Scenes from life (Box 240, Folder 3849)
        - With Marie-Louise (Box 240, Folder 3850)
        - With his marshals (Box 240, Folder 3851)
        - Death bed, last moments, and grave (Box 240, Folder 3852)
        - Statues (Box 240, Folder 3853)
      - Napoleon III, Emperor of the French, 1808-1873 (Box 240, Folder 3854)
      - Piombino, Elisa Bonaparte Baciocchi, principessa di, 1777-1820 (Box 240, Folder 3855)
      - Other Bonapartes (Box 240, Folder 3856)
      - Oversize
        - Bonaparte, Carlo Maria - Marie Louise, 16 (Box 241 (Oversize), Folder 3857-3872)
        - Napoleon I, 9 (Box 242 (Oversize), Folder 3873-3881)
        - Napoleon I - Other Bonapartes, 8 (Box 243 (Oversize), Folder 3882-3889)
    - Other European rulers and ruling families
      - Anjou
        - House of Anjou (general) (Box 244, Folder 3890)
        - René I, King of Naples and Jerusalem, 1409-1480 (Box 244, Folder 3891)
      - Bourbon
        - House of Bourbon (general), 2 (Box 244, Folder 3892-3893)
        - Bourbon, Charles, duc de, 1490-1527 (Box 244, Folder 3894)
        - Antoine de Bourbon, King of Navarre, 1518-1562 (Box 244, Folder 3895)
        - Condé, Louis, prince de, 1530-1569 (Box 244, Folder 3896)
        - Condé, Henri I de Bourbon, prince de, 1552-1588 (Box 244, Folder 3897)
        - Conti, Armand de Bourbon, prince de, 1629-1666 (Box 244, Folder 3898)
        - Conti, François Louis de Bourbon, prince de, 1664-1709 (Box 244, Folder 3899)
        - Louis, Duke of Burgundy, Dauphin of France, 1682-1712 (Box 244, Folder 3900)
        - Maine, Louis Auguste de Bourbon, Duc de, 1670-1736 (Box 244, Folder 3901)
        - Condé, Louis Henri de Bourbon, prince de, 1692-1740 (Box 244, Folder 3902)
        - Conti, Louis François de Bourbon, prince de, 1717-1776 (Box 244, Folder 3903)
        - Condé, Louis Joseph de Bourbon, prince de, 1736-1818 (Box 244, Folder 3904)
      - Orange and Nassau
        - House of Orange (general), 2 (Box 245, Folder 3905-3906)
        - William I, Prince of Orange, 1533-1584 (Box 245, Folder 3907)
        - Filips Willem, Prince of Orange, 1554-1618 (Box 245, Folder 3908)
        - Willem Lodewijk, Count of Nassau, 1560-1620 (Box 245, Folder 3909)
        - Maurice, Prince of Orange, 1567-1625 (Box 245, Folder 3910)
        - Frederick Henry, Prince of Orange, 1584-1647 (Box 245, Folder 3911)
        - Johan Maurits, Prince of Nassau-Siegen, 1604-1679 (Box 245, Folder 3912)
        - William II, Prince of Orange, 1626-1650 (Box 245, Folder 3913)
        - William I, King of the Netherlands, 1772-1843 (Box 245, Folder 3914)
      - Orleans
        - House of Orleans (general), 2 (Box 245, Folder 3915-3916)
        - Visconti, Valentine, duchesse d' Orléans, 1366-1408 (Box 245, Folder 3917)
        - Longueville, Henri d'Orléans, duc de, 1595-1663 (Box 245, Folder 3918)
        - Orléans, Marie de Bourbon, princesse de Dombes, duchesse de Montpensier et d', 1605-1627 (Box 245, Folder 3919)
        - Orléans, Gaston, duc d', 1608-1660 (Box 245, Folder 3920)
        - Orléans, Marguerite de Lorraine, duchesse d', 1615-1672 (Box 245, Folder 3921)
        - Orléans, Henriette-Anne, duchesse d', 1644-1670 (Box 246, Folder 3922)
        - Bourbon-Penthièvre, Louise-Marie-Adélaïde de, duchesse d'Orléans, 1753-1821 (Box 246, Folder 3923)
        - Orléans, Louis Philippe Joseph, duc d', 1747-1793 (Box 246, Folder 3924)
        - Orléans, Ferdinand-Philippe-Louis-Charles-Henri, duc d', 1810-1842 (Box 246, Folder 3925)
      - Prussia
        - Prussia (general) (Box 246, Folder 3926)
        - Frederick II, King of Prussia, 1712-1786 (Box 246, Folder 3927)
        - Frederick William II, King of Prussia, 1744-1797 (Box 246, Folder 3928)
        - Frederick William III, King of Prussia, 1770-1840 (Box 246, Folder 3929)
      - Russia
        - Russia (general) (Box 246, Folder 3930)
        - Peter I, Emperor of Russia, 1672-1725 (Box 246, Folder 3931)
        - Catherine II, Empress of Russia, 1729-1796 (Box 246, Folder 3932)
        - Paul I, Emperor of Russia, 1754-1801 (Box 246, Folder 3933)
        - Alexander I, Emperor of Russia, 1777-1825 (Box 246, Folder 3934)
      - Spain
        - Spain (general) (Box 247, Folder 3935)
        - Philip I, King of Castile, 1478-1506 (Box 247, Folder 3936)
        - Philip II, King of Spain, 1527-1598 (Box 247, Folder 3937)
        - Philip III, King of Spain, 1578-1621 (Box 247, Folder 3938)
        - Philip IV, King of Spain, 1605-1665 (Box 247, Folder 3939)
        - Philip V, King of Spain, 1683-1746 (Box 247, Folder 3940)
        - Charles, King of Spain (all) (Box 247, Folder 3941)
        - Marie Louise, of Orléans, Queen, consort of Charles II, King of Spain, 1662-1689 (Box 247, Folder 3942)
      - Sweden
        - Sweden (general) (Box 247, Folder 3943)
        - Gustav I Vasa, King of Sweden, 1496-1560 (Box 247, Folder 3944)
        - Gustav II Adolf, King of Sweden, 1594-1632 (Box 247, Folder 3945)
        - Gustav III, King of Sweden, 1746-1792 (Box 247, Folder 3946)
        - Charles XIV John, King of Sweden and Norway, 1763-1844 (Box 247, Folder 3947)
        - Gustav IV Adolf, King of Sweden, 1778-1837 (Box 247, Folder 3948)
        - Charles, King of Sweden (other) (Box 247, Folder 3949)
      - Other monarchs, A-Z
        - Albert / Albrecht (Box 248, Folder 3950)
        - Alexander (Box 248, Folder 3951)
        - Alfonso / Alfonsus (Box 248, Folder 3952)
        - Anthony / Antony / Antonius (Box 248, Folder 3953)
        - Ann / Anne / Annabella (Box 248, Folder 3954)
        - Arthur (Box 248, Folder 3955)
        - Augusta (Box 248, Folder 3956)
        - Blanche of Castile, Queen, consort of Louis VIII, King of France (Box 248, Folder 3957)
        - Charlemagne, Emperor, 742-814 (Box 248, Folder 3958)
        - Charles / Carlo / Carl (Box 248, Folder 3959)
        - Charles V, Holy Roman Emperor, 1500-1558 (Box 248, Folder 3960)
        - Charlotte (Box 248, Folder 3961)
        - Christian, King of Denmark, Norway, and Sweden (all) (Box 248, Folder 3962)
        - David (Box 248, Folder 3963)
        - Dirk (Box 248, Folder 3964)
        - Donald (Box 248, Folder 3965)
        - Duncan (Box 248, Folder 3966)
        - Eleanor (Box 248, Folder 3967)
        - Elizabeth (Box 248, Folder 3968)
        - Emanuel / Emmanuel (Box 248, Folder 3969)
        - Ferdinand / Fernando (Box 249, Folder 3970)
        - Francis I, Emperor of Austria, 1768-1835 (Box 249, Folder 3971)
        - Frederick (Box 249, Folder 3972)
        - Frederick Augustus of Saxony (Box 249, Folder 3973)
        - George (Box 249, Folder 3974)
        - Henry / Henri (Box 249, Folder 3975)
        - Isabel / Isabelle / Isabella (Box 249, Folder 3976)
        - James (Box 249, Folder 3977)
        - Louis / Ludwig (Box 249, Folder 3978)
        - Jeanne / Joan / Joanna / Giovanna (Box 249, Folder 3979)
        - John / Jean / Johannes (Box 249, Folder 3980)
        - Joseph (Box 249, Folder 3981)
        - Joseph I, Holy Roman Emperor, 1678-1711 (Box 250, Folder 3982)
        - Joseph II, Holy Roman Emperor, 1741-1790, and Josepha, 2 (Box 250, Folder 3983-3984)
        - Leopold (Box 250, Folder 3985)
        - Léopold I, King of the Belgians, 1790-1865 (Box 250, Folder 3986)
        - Leopold II, Holy Roman Emperor, 1747-1792 (Box 250, Folder 3987)
        - Lorraine (Box 250, Folder 3988)
        - Louis, Dauphin of France, 1729-1765
        - Louise (Box 250, Folder 3989)
        - Louisa (Box 250, Folder 3990)
        - Margaret / Marguerite (Box 250, Folder 3991)
        - Marguerite, Queen, consort of Henry II, King of Navarre, 1492-1549 (Box 250, Folder 3992)
        - Maria / Marie (Box 250, Folder 3993)
        - Maria Theresa, Empress of Austria, 1717-1780 (Box 250, Folder 3994)
        - Maria Theresa, of Naples-Sicily, Empress, consort of Francis I, Emperor of Austria, -1807 (Box 250, Folder 3995)
        - Maria Theresa (other) (Box 250, Folder 3996)
        - Marie Ann / Marie Anna (Box 250, Folder 3997)
        - Mary (Box 251, Folder 3998)
        - Matilda (Box 251, Folder 3999)
        - Matthew / Matthias (Box 251, Folder 4000)
        - Maximilian, Holy Roman Emperor (all) (Box 251, Folder 4001)
        - Merovee (Box 251, Folder 4002)
        - Pedro I, Emperor of Brazil, 1798-1834 (Box 251, Folder 4003)
        - Philip / Philippe (Box 251, Folder 4004)
        - Raoul (Box 251, Folder 4005)
        - Robert / Rupert (Box 251, Folder 4006)
        - Rudolph / Rodolphe (Box 251, Folder 4007)
        - Sanctius (Box 251, Folder 4008)
        - Stanislaus (Box 251, Folder 4009)
        - Theodoric / Thierry, counts of Holland (Box 251, Folder 4010)
        - Victor Emmanuel (all) (Box 251, Folder 4011)
        - William / Wilhelm (Box 251, Folder 4012)
        - Miscellaneous, 4 (Box 251, Folder 4013-4016)
        - Oversize
          - House of Anjou - Orléans, Gaston, 24 (Box 252 (Oversize), Folder 4017-4040)
          - Orléans, Henriette - Frederick Augustus, 22 (Box 253 (Oversize), Folder 4041-4062)
          - George - Miscellaneous, 21 (Box 254 (Oversize), Folder 4063-4083)
          - Louise - Miscellaneous, 20 (Box 255 (Oversize), Folder 4084-4103)
  - Non-Western Rulers and Figures
    Contains images of rulers, military figures, religious leaders, and notable citizens from countries other than Europe, the British Isles, and the United States, though the prints were generally published in those places. Due to their small quantity relative to the rest of the collection, they were isolated for ease of access.
    - Africa (Box 256, Folder 4104)
    - Arabia (Box 256, Folder 4105)
    - China (Box 256, Folder 4106)
    - Egypt (Box 256, Folder 4107)
    - Haiti (Box 256, Folder 4108)
    - Japan (Box 256, Folder 4109)
    - Mexico (Box 256, Folder 4110)
    - Pacific Islands (Box 256, Folder 4111)
    - Persia (Box 256, Folder 4112)
    - Peru (Box 256, Folder 4113)
    - South Asia (Box 256, Folder 4114)
    - Southeast Asia (Box 256, Folder 4115)
    - Turkey / The Levant, 4 (Box 256, Folder 4116-4119)
    - Oversize
      - Africa - Turkey, 11 (Box 257 (Oversize), Folder 4120-4130)
  - Catholic Church Leaders
    - Pope. Adrian (all) (Box 258, Folder 4131)
    - Pope. Gregory (all) (Box 258, Folder 4132)
    - Pope. Innocent (all) (Box 258, Folder 4133)
    - Pope. John (all) (Box 258, Folder 4134)
    - Pope. Julius (all) (Box 258, Folder 4135)
    - Pope. Leo (all) (Box 258, Folder 4136)
  - Classical Figures: Historical
    This subseries contains figures from Greek or Roman history, mainly 1) rulers, military leaders, emperors and senators, and 2) writers, historians and philosophers, including writers whose works we have, though we have little or no concrete historical information of their lives (e.g., Homer). Figures have their own folders if prints were numerous, or the figures were particularly well-known and therefore researchers were likely to look for their names. In the case of writers, folders contain portraits of the writers themselves rather than their subjects (i.e., prints showing images of Homer, not images from the works; for depictions of the Iliad or Odyssey, look under Homer in the Classical Figures Mythological subseries). Folders may also contain images of the figures' wives and children. For information on historical figures, use the Oxford Classical Dictionary Online. Unidentified emperors are filed under "Caesar."
    Following the A - Z general files are two folders holding plates from Thomas Worlidge's three-volume work, A Select Collection of Drawings, from curious antique gems, most of them in the possession of the nobility and gentry of this kingdom. Etched after the manner of Rembrandt. (London and Bath, 1768). Many have images of historical and mythological figures, as well as other historical iconography.
    - A - P, 7 (Box 259, Folder 4137-4143)
    - R - Z, 3 (Box 260, Folder 4144-4146)
    - Plates from Thomas Worlidge, A Select Collection of Drawings, from curious antique gems (London, Printed by D. Leach for M. Worlidge and M. Wicksteed, Bath, 1768), 2 (Box 260, Folder 4147-4148)
    - Aeschines (Box 261, Folder 4149)
    - Aeschylus (Box 261, Folder 4150)
    - Aesop (Box 261, Folder 4151)
    - Agesilaus II, King of Sparta (Box 261, Folder 4152)
    - Agrippa, Marcus Vipsanius (Box 261, Folder 4153)
    - Agrippina (Box 261, Folder 4154)
    - Alcibiades (Box 261, Folder 4155)
    - Alexander, the Great, 356-323 B.C. (Box 261, Folder 4156)
    - Anacreon (Box 261, Folder 4157)
    - Antiochus (Box 261, Folder 4158)
    - Antinoüs, ca. 110-130 (Box 261, Folder 4159)
    - Antoninus Pius, Emperor of Rome, 86-161 (Box 261, Folder 4160)
    - Antonius, Marcus, 83?-30 B.C. (Box 261, Folder 4161)
    - Aratus, of Sicyon, 271-213 B.C. (Box 261, Folder 4162)
    - Aristides (Box 261, Folder 4163)
    - Aristotle (Box 261, Folder 4164)
    - Aristophanes (Box 261, Folder 4165)
    - Arsaces (Box 261, Folder 4166)
    - Artaxerxes (Box 261, Folder 4167)
    - Augustus, Emperor of Rome, 63 B.C.-14 A.D. (Box 261, Folder 4168)
    - Belisarius, ca. 505-565 (Box 261, Folder 4169)
    - Boadicea, Queen, d. 62 (Box 261, Folder 4170)
    - Brutus, Marcus Junius, 85?-42 B.C. (Box 261, Folder 4171)
    - Caesar (Box 261, Folder 4172)
    - Caesar, Julius (Box 261, Folder 4173)
    - Caligula, Emperor of Rome, 12-41 (Box 261, Folder 4174)
    - Camillus (Box 261, Folder 4175)
    - Caracalla, Emperor of Rome, 188-217 (Box 261, Folder 4176)
    - Cato, Marcus Porcius, 234-149 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4177)
    - Cicero, Marcus Tullius (Box 262, Folder 4178)
    - Claudius, Emperor of Rome, 10 B.C.-54 A.D. (Box 262, Folder 4179)
    - Cleopatra, Queen of Egypt, d. 30 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4180)
    - Constantine I, Emperor of Rome, d. 337 (Box 262, Folder 4181)
    - Demetrius (Box 262, Folder 4182)
    - Democritus, ca. 460-ca. 370 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4183)
    - Demosthenes (Box 262, Folder 4184)
    - Diogenes, d. ca. 323 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4185)
    - Dion, ca. 408 B.C.-354 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4186)
    - Dionysius (Box 262, Folder 4187)
    - Domitian, Emperor of Rome, 51-96 (Box 262, Folder 4188)
    - Domitius Ahenobarbus, Cn., active 104-89 B.C. (Nero) and Octavia (Box 262, Folder 4189)
    - Drusus, Nero Claudius, 38-9 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4190)
    - Epaminondas, ca. 420 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4191)
    - Epicurus (Box 262, Folder 4192)
    - Eumenes (Box 262, Folder 4193)
    - Euripides (Box 262, Folder 4194)
    - Fabius (Box 262, Folder 4195)
    - Flaminius, Gaius, d. 217 B.C. (Box 262, Folder 4196)
    - Galba, Servius Sulpicius, Emperor of Rome, 3 B.C.-69 A.D. (Box 262, Folder 4197)
    - Germanicus Caesar, 15 B.C.-19 A.D. (Box 262, Folder 4198)
    - Gracchus (Box 262, Folder 4199)
    - Hadrian, Emperor of Rome, 76-138 (Box 263, Folder 4200)
    - Hannibal, 247-182 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4201)
    - Heraclitus, of Ephesus (Box 263, Folder 4202)
    - Herodotus (Box 263, Folder 4203)
    - Hesiod (Box 263, Folder 4204)
    - Homer (Box 263, Folder 4205)
    - Horace (Box 263, Folder 4206)
    - Isocrates (Box 263, Folder 4207)
    - Juba (Box 263, Folder 4208)
    - Lepidus, Marcus Aemilius, d. 13 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4209)
    - Leonidas (Box 263, Folder 4210)
    - Livy (Box 263, Folder 4211)
    - Lucullus, ca. 117 B.C.-ca. 56 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4212)
    - Lycurgus, ca. 390-ca. 324 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4213)
    - Lysander, d. 395 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4214)
    - Lysias (Box 263, Folder 4215)
    - Lysimachus, King of Thrace, ca. 361-281 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4216)
    - Maecenas, Gaius Cilnius, ca. 70 B.C.-8 B.C (Box 263, Folder 4217)
    - Marcellus (Box 263, Folder 4218)
    - Marcus Aurelius, Emperor of Rome, 121-180 (Box 263, Folder 4219)
    - Marius, Gaius, ca. 157 B.C.-86 B.C (Box 263, Folder 4220)
    - Mihrdād, King of the Parthians (all) (Box 263, Folder 4221)
    - Miltiades, ca. 550 B.C.-489 B.C (Box 263, Folder 4222)
    - Nicias (Box 263, Folder 4223)
    - Numa Pompilius, King of Rome, active 715-673 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4224)
    - Otho, Marcus Salvius, Emperor of Rome, 32-69 (Box 263, Folder 4225)
    - Ovid, 43 B.C.-17 or 18 A.D. (Box 263, Folder 4226)
    - Pelopidas, d. 364 B.C. (Box 263, Folder 4227)
    - Periander (Box 263, Folder 4228)
    - Pericles, ca. 495-429 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4229)
    - Perseus, King of Macedonia (Box 264, Folder 4230)
    - Persius (Box 264, Folder 4231)
    - Petronius Arbiter (Box 264, Folder 4232)
    - Phaedrus (Box 264, Folder 4233)
    - Philip II, King of Macedonia, 382-336 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4234)
    - Phocion, d. 318 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4235)
    - Pindar (Box 264, Folder 4236)
    - Pittacus, of Mytilene, ca. 650-ca. 570 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4237)
    - Plato (Box 264, Folder 4238)
    - Plutarch (Box 264, Folder 4239)
    - Pompey, the Great, 106-48 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4240)
    - Propertius, Sextus (Box 264, Folder 4241)
    - Ptolemy (all) (Box 264, Folder 4242)
    - Pyrrhus, King of Epirus, 318-272 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4243)
    - Pythagoras (Box 264, Folder 4244)
    - Regulus, Marcus Atilius, d. 250? B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4245)
    - Sallust, 86-34 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4246)
    - Sappho (Box 264, Folder 4247)
    - Scipio, Africanus, ca. 236-183 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4248)
    - Seneca, Lucius Annaeus, ca. 4 B.C.-65 A.D. (Box 264, Folder 4249)
    - Sertorius, d. 72 B.C. (Box 264, Folder 4250)
    - Severus (Box 264, Folder 4251)
    - Socrates (Box 264, Folder 4252)
    - Sophocles (Box 264, Folder 4253)
    - Terence (Box 264, Folder 4254)
    - Themistocles, circa 524 B.C.-circa 459 B.C. (Box 265, Folder 4255)
    - Thucydides (Box 265, Folder 4256)
    - Tiberius
    - Timoleon, ca. 411-337 B.C.
    - Titus, Emperor of Rome, 40-81 (Box 265, Folder 4257)
    - Trajan, Emperor of Rome, 53-117 (Box 265, Folder 4258)